so let's assume I know a lot of
vulnerability types but I've never dated
back bounty how would you recommend me
to start
the best place to start really is we're
looking at resources around bug bonding
it's obviously yourself you've got
things like provide context around what
blog bound is and and what different
things are finding what you really like
hacking is is probably the best advice I
could give you know you have wide scope
programs that allow a bunch of assets or
everything owned by the company you have
really small applications that you know
you need to go deep in so understanding
what you enjoyed is part of your job is
probably the best thing best advice I
could give because what you enjoy doing
is is generally what you're going to be
better at I think the most important
thing is understanding the bug Bounty
space you know how it differs slightly
from Penn testing understanding what you
really like doing from your pen testing
background and persistence obviously
because there's probably three four
months where you're not going to find
anything sometimes even longer but I
mean as if you stick with something
you've got a higher chance of finding
something then than just switching about
all the time